Here we go
It's its its the life i choose
gunshots in the dark,
one eye closed
And we got it cooking like
a one- eyed stove
You can catch me kissing my girl
with both eyes closed
Perfecting my passion,
thanks for asking
Couldn't slow down so
we had to crash it
You used plastic, we 'bout cash
I see some people ahead that we gon' pass
YEAH!!!
I never feared death or dying
I only fear never trying
I am whatever I am
Only God can judge me , now
One shot, everything rides on
Tonight even if I 've got
Three strikes I'mma go for it
This moment , we own it
And I' m not to be played with
Because it can get dangerous
see these people I ride with
This moment , we own it
And the same ones that I ride with
be the same ones that I die with
put it all out on the line with
if you looking for me you can find Wiz
In the new car or in the crown with
my new broad , thats a fine chick
And the wonder squad, I' m down with
Ain' t no way around it
What you say , tell me what you say
working hard ,reppin for my dogs ,do this everyday
stuck to the plan
always think that we would
stand up, never ran
we the fam and loyalty
never change up
been down since day one,
look at where we came from
Jumpin out on anybody who
try to say some
one thing about it
got a problem, i got the same one
money rolls, we fold
plenty clubs we closed
follow the same code
never turn our backs, our cars
dont even lose control
One shot, everything rides on
tonight even if I 've got
three strikes, I'mma go for it
this moment, we own it
And I' m not to be played with
Because it can get dangerous
see these people i ride with
this moment, we own it